upstartblogger.com 2008-12-16

# Upstart Blogger | Privacy Policy

### About The Information We Collect

We only collect personal information from you that you provide voluntarily.

We may collect information when you place an order, sign up for a newsletter, request information, or fill out a form on our Web site.

We may collect and share aggregate information about our visitors. For example, we may say that 50% of our visitors are Mac users. We use this information to customize our content and advertising.

We may disclose information about you when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or when disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to others or interfering with Upstart Blogger’s rights or property.

In the event of an assignment, sale, joint venture, or other transfer or disposition of some or all of the assets of Upstart Blogger, you agree that we can accordingly assign, sell, license or transfer any information that you have provided to us. Please note, however, that the purchasing party can not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Notice in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Notice without your prior consent.

### Opting Out

You may choose not to receive any email from us.

### Use of Cookies

Upstart Blogger may uses cookies to track visitor usage. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use most of the Upstart Blogger Web site.

While visiting Upstart Blogger, you may receive cookies from our advertisers or sponsors. Upstart Blogger does not control these cookies or use the associated data.

### Security of Information

The security of our your personally identifiable information is of the highest priority. We do our best to provide security of your information when visiting our site. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or through our Services, and you do so at your own risk.

### Changes to this Notice

We may change this Privacy Notice from time to time. Be assured that even if the Privacy Notice changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Notice in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Notice without your prior consent.

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to robert [at] upstartblogger [dot] com.
